var questions = [{
    "question": "Saylani Mass IT training manager ?",
    "option1": "Ghous Ahmed",
    "option2": "Basit Ali",
    "option3": "Muhammad Ali Mughal",
    "option4": "Wajid Ullah",
    "answer": "3"
}, {
    "question": "the major language of world wide web is ?",
    "option1": "html",
    "option2": "php",
    "option3": "css",
    "option4": "java",
    "answer": "1"
}, {
    "question": "URL is abbrevviation of  ?",
    "option1": "Universal Resources Locator",
    "option2": "Uniform Resources Locator",
    "option3": "Univer Resources Locator",
    "option4": "none",
    "answer": "2"
},{
    "question": "The network in which we connect each network node to a central device (hub) is called?",
    "option1": "Bus Network topology",
    "option2": "Star Network topology ",
    "option3": "  Rining topology",
    "option4": "none",
    "answer": "2"
}, {
    "question": "FTP is an abbreviation of ?",
    "option1": " File Transfer Position ",
    "option2": " File Transfer protection",
    "option3": " File Transfer protocol",
    "option4": " File Transfer possibility",
    "answer": "3"
}, {
    "question": "A virus that replicaties itself is called",
    "option1": "bug",
    "option2": "worm",
    "option3": " bomb",
    "option4": "hoax",
    "answer": "1"
}, {
    "question": "File compression utilties can reduce the file size by",
    "option1": " 10%",
    "option2": " 60%",
    "option3": " 80% ",
    "option4": "100%",
    "answer": "3"
}, {
    "question": " In C language , .exe file is produced by ?",
    "option1": "Linker ",
    "option2": "loader ",
    "option3": " compiler ",
    "option4": "interpreter",
    "answer": "1"
}, {
    "question": "The number of Bytes used by char data type in C is ?",
    "option1": "1",
    "option2": "2",
    "option3": "4",
    "option4": "3",
    "answer": "1"
}, {
    "question": "What does the prefix pico means ? ",
    "option1": "Hunderdth",
    "option2": "Millionth",
    "option3": "Billionth",
    "option4": "Trillionth",
    "answer": "4"
}

]